MARIO PEREZ

North Hollywood, CA 91606 (909)261-0610 Marsmario96@gmail.com

Constantly improving my weaknesses, always listening, and learning from others or by experience. Strong passion for IT and computers, with a can-do attitude. Great customer service experience and will go above and beyond with any given task.

Skills

- Proficient in Microsoft Windows (7-10), MacOS, and iOS
- Experience in virtualization and remote desktop
- Some experience with Windows Server 2016
- Have personally built and managed multiple computers

Experience

Bingo West /Computer Troubleshooter and Delivery DriverOCTOBER 2016 - PRESENT, RANCHO CUCAMONGA

Experience in virus removal, internet connectivity troubleshooting, SOHO network setup, hardware replacement, and more.

Transporting large amounts of bingo supplies to schools, senior centers, casinos, and churches. Handling cash or check payments after delivery or repair is completed.

DCX-CHOL / Electrical Cable Tester

May 2014- January 2015, Los Angeles

Formally assured that all proper tools and safety precautions are in place to start the job. Testing of electrical components and making sure all cables are working before they are sent off to complex projects.

Ontario Airport / Airport Ramp Worker

August 2013 - December 2013, Ontario

Unloading and loading of airplane luggage, as well as assisting handicapped customers towards their desired location.

Education

Western Governors University/ In Progress: Cloud Computing 2020, Online

Chaffey College, Some College / No Degree: Computer Science

2015 - 2016, Rancho Cucamonga

Graduated Los Osos High School

2014, Rancho Cucamonga

Certifications

CompTIA A+ Certified I.T Technician

(Currently working on becoming Network+ Certified)